Translated by Releska
Thank you for watching.
I'm worried about my throat.
I'll do my best to sing in a cute voice.
I'm nervous.
I'm about to collapse.
Are you okay?
I'm nervous.
I'm going to get a fan.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll drop a few people at the show.
I'm nervous.
Please come up to the stage.
Please give me a big hand.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm TZ Hamburger.
I'm 154 cm tall and have a small body.
But my size is 25 cm.
I'm a taekwondo player.
I'll show you my special skill.
I'll do my best to make you happy.
My favorite food is broccoli.
I had a hair cut by a hairdresser.
How do you like it?
Thank you.
I'm a big fan of you.
I'm like a cat.
I'm meeting you for the first time
today.
Please love me.
Leave it to me.
I'm like a curry bun.
You can love me.
I'm Yukachi, Yukachi, Yukachi's PIN.
I'm Rikiegel, with a score of 100.
The center is Barona.
Thank you.
I love you all.
I love you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Today is my birthday.
I'm your idol, the strongest twin tail.
Please remember me.
I missed you all.
Hello, everyone.
I love you.
I want to make everyone happy.
My specialty is 5mm.
Can you see it?
I'm your cute girl, Ruffalo.
I'm here to do something.
Please look at me.
I'm in this city from city to city.
It's a busy city.
Our language.
I'm going to be on stage a little while
ago.
Now I'm standing here.
Makuhari.
Thank you.
3... 2... 1...
audition for part time
Thank you for watching!